easycabs.com 2015-04-25

# Carzonrent - Privacy and Policy

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") discloses the privacy practices for Carzonrent (India) Private Limited ("Carzonrent") website ("website"). Carzonrent places paramount importance on maintaining the privacy of its customers'("User") personal information under the applicable laws in India.  
Please read this Policy carefully by accessing or using our website. The User hereby acknowledges that he has read, understood, and agrees to be bound to all the terms of this Policy and our website's terms of use before the User proceeds.  

##  Personal Information- What personal information is collected from the user?

Carzonrent collects and uses relevant personal information of User in order to provide services. The following personal information ("information") is collected from the User and shall include ,though not limited to, the User's street address, name, contact telephone number; vehicle preference; company name and employee accounts with Carzorent; Reservations and Rental details including dates, times and places of vehicle hire; ; online feedback surveys; electronic records/databases of all rental agreements;

##  How this information will be used by the company

The collection of information shall depend upon on the User's use of Carzonrent's services. Carzonrent may collect information directly from the User by mobile devices, portable devices (Tablet) /telephone/fax/email/over the counter/filling an enrollment form or through an internet based service.  
The User may choose not to provide some information but this may prevent Carzonrent from providing the standard of services that is normally expected.  
Carzonrent protects information by keeping up to date with techniques and processes meeting current industry standards ensuring that information are kept secure and confidential. Only employees of Carzonrent and those who perform services on their behalf shall be authorized to handle & have access to the information.  
Carzonrent shall be careful in the management of information of Users and also has measures in place to ensure that collected information is protected and not accessed inappropriately. Carzonrent makes every effort to ensure that information of User is accurate and updated and requires User to verify their identity for security purposes before replying to any requests.

##  How the company transfers data to third party companies?

Carzonrent does not submit information to third parties except in the following cases:

  1. Receive permission of the User.
  2. On outsourcing activities, wherein Carzonrent ensures that strict management of the information is enforced through a separately executed non-disclosure agreement.
  3. Disclosure of information in order to comply with the law or a court order; enforce or apply this Policy, our website terms of use or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others.
  4. On sharing of information in a Business Transfer i.e. in case of a merger with, or be acquired by another company.
  5. In good faith so as to protect the property of Carzonrent, or to protect the safety of employees and their families.

Any information provided to or gathered by this website is controlled primarily by Carzonrent, whose registered office is at E-4, Rani Jhansi Road, Jhandewalan Extension, and New Delhi-110055.

##  Cookies

Carzonrent stores cookies on the User's computer in order to facilitate and customize the experience with the Website. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a User's computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. Cookies are used to save time while using the website, tracking and targeting User interests in order to provide a customized experience. Carzonrent may use Third Party Advertising Companies to display advertisements on the Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on the User's computer. This Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser. The User may be able to modify the browser settings to decline cookies. The User notes that on modifications of cookies, some parts of the website may not work properly.

##  Security

The access is through user Id and password. The storage of information of the User is in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. As transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, Carzonrent shall strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect User's information. Carzonrent hereby states that it does not guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the website, and is not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

##  Links to other sites

The Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Carzonrent. The User needs to be aware that Carzonrent shall not be responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. Therefore Carzonrent encourages the User to be aware on leaving the website and read the privacy statements of each and every other site that collects information. This Policy applies only to information collected by this website.

##  How to edit this information or log out?

The access to users account is through user ID login and passwords and Carzonrent persuades that the user promptly updates information if it changes in order to help Carzonrent keep the information and up to date. The access would be withdrawn if such facility is not to be continued.  
However, Carzonrent keeps track of past transactions, therefore the User cannot delete information or opt-out of information associated with past transactions on the website.

##  Changes or Modifications to the Policy

The changes made herein to the Policy shall be made without prior notice under the heading "Privacy Policy" section of the Website. The revised Policy is effective immediately when posted on the website. The User's continued use of the website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute the User's acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Policy. 

##  Disclaimer

Every effort has been made to ensure that the information on this site is correct and up to date, however, Carzonrent does not provide any warranty as to the completeness or accuracy of the information and, subject to applicable laws, does not accept any liability for damages of any kind resulting from the access or use of this website and its contents.  
All information on this site is protected by copyright and other intellectual property rights. No images, text or other content from this site may be distributed or reproduced without prior written approval from Carzonrent.

##  Contact Us

In case of any questions or suggestions regarding the Policy, please email Carzonrent at: [corporate@carzonrent.com](mailto:corporate@carzonrent.com)
